{
    "subject": "Leonid_Trauberg",
    "predicate": "directed",
    "object": "The_Youth_of_Maxim",
    "human_readable": "Leonid Trauberg directed the film The Youth of Maxim.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8873511552810669,
            "question": "Who directed the film 'The Youth of Maxim'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8050563335418701,
            "question": "What is the name of the film directed by Leonid Trauberg?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6235839128494263,
            "question": "Are there any other films directed by Leonid Trauberg?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5600046515464783,
            "question": "Where was 'The Youth of Maxim' filmed?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5288936495780945,
            "question": "Is 'The Youth of Maxim' a fictional or biographical film?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5195839405059814,
            "question": "Who are some of the actors in 'The Youth of Maxim'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4982726275920868,
            "question": "What is the story about in 'The Youth of Maxim'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.49721819162368774,
            "question": "What genre is the film 'The Youth of Maxim' likely to be?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4162641167640686,
            "question": "What year was 'The Youth of Maxim' released?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3964702785015106,
            "question": "What themes might be explored in 'The Youth of Maxim'?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Leonid Trauberg directed the film The Youth of Maxim.",
            "html": "yago_17904_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What year was 'The Youth of Maxim' released?",
            "html": "yago_17904_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What genre is the film 'The Youth of Maxim' likely to be?",
            "html": "yago_17904_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the story about in 'The Youth of Maxim'?",
            "html": "yago_17904_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "yago_17904_13.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_17904_22.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_17904_30.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_17904_33.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_17904_41.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_17904_55.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_17904_58.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_17904_64.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_17904_70.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_17904_72.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe information in the documents supports this triple. The documents state that:\n\n* Grigori Kozintsev and Leonid Trauberg directed the film \"The Youth of Maxim\" (file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/yago_17904/re-ranker-msmarco/65.txt)\n* This film is also referred to as \"The Youth of Maxim\" (file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/yago_17904/re-ranker-msmarco/59.txt), implying that it was directed by the same people.\n* There is no information in the provided documents that contradicts this triple."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\nThe documents provide information about Leonid Trauberg and his work on the film \"The Youth of Maxim,\" confirming that he was indeed one of the directors."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "mistral-nemo": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "-",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}